doesn't uh they've got copyright things
so you know if you're doing someone
else's song um they don't like that
unless there are ways to get permission
to do it and uh thank you someone's
there over there that's got the clap
hope he's all right
anyway so I'm going just do some
originals for now uh let's see what else
do I got um hold on I'm going to look up
my little list here you recording
already.
>> I am.
>> You are. Okay. Hi there. Hi all you
people out in uh world world land. Um
[snorts] my my name's Dove in case you
didn't know and now you know. Uh and I
just got time for a couple more songs
and I'm going to do a couple of
originals soon as I can figure out how
to use this phone. I've never had a
phone before. Um
I'm going to my list of originals.
There we go. There we go.
Okay, there it is. Um,
>> so what I got now? How many more
minutes?
>> Five minutes. All right. I'm going to do
the first song that came to me here on
Maui
um back in 2002.
And it's about uh the main path of my
life is a spiritual path. And this song
is about uh us all
becoming conscious of our connection
with the divine god etc. Um and it goes
like this.
We found our lost love tonight.
And it sure feels so right.
[music]
And in the morning's new light,
you are looking [music]
so dear
in the hold of your arms.
Life could do us no [music] harm
and we [music] are feeling so warm.
Oh we love [music] you God dear.
[music]
In this love light, we find
the love [singing and music] that's
divine.
We are [music] feeling so fine
just to have you [music] so near
in the hold of your arms.
[music]
Life could do us no [music] harm
and we are feeling so warm.
[music]
Oh, we love you God dear.
Ooh.
[music]
Oo. [music]
[singing]
Oh.
[music] Oh.
>> [music]
>> Oh.
Oh. [music]
[music]
In [music] this music we find
the love that's [music and singing]
divine.
And we are feeling [music]
so fine.
And just to [music] have you so near
[singing]
[music]
in the hold of your arms.
Life could do us [music] no harm.
And we are [music] feeling so warm.
>> [music]
>> Oh, we love you, [singing] God. Dearoo.
[music] Ooh.
Ooh.
Oh, [music]
we found our lost love tonight.
And it sure [music] feels so right.
And in the [music] morning's new light.
[music]
Oh, we love [singing] you, God, dear.
Thank you. Thank you very much. We're
going to bring up Chino La Forge,
who's the founder of the uh comedy
simulator, which this is, and the host
>> and
again, my name is Dove. And there's a
lot more room here in this guitar case
if you want, you know, anything you want
to put in there. Um, and here he comes,
ladies and gentlemen. Let's have a big
hand for the founder of the comedy
simulator, Chino La Forge.
And keep it going for Dove, ladies and
gentlemen. Keep it going for Dove, our
[applause]
opening musician.
Oh, these these lights look crispy.
Looks like they fixed them. Wonderful.
Hey, ladies and gentlemen, give it up
for Pa Bay Coffee and Bar letting us do
this [applause]
wild show that we do every Monday. Hold
on, let me fix the speaker real quick.
>> That's right. I just got to angle it out
to avoid the feedback. All right. Uh,
welcome to Pa Bay. that. Welcome to the
comedy simulator, ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome, welcome, welcome. Who's Who's
been to the comedy simulator before?
>> Who's never been to the comedy
simulator? Welcome, welcome, fresh,
fresh people. Wonderful. Who didn't know
that there was comedy tonight and it's
just kind of happening at you right now?
Anybody? Okay, cool. Everybody's cool.
All right, wonderful. Sometimes it
happens. It gets kind of weird. Doesn't
have to be weird. We all know it's
coming. My name is Chino. I'm your host
of the Comedy Simulator. And it is
called the comedy simulator because this
is not your usual standup comedy show.
This is a simulated comedy experience.
What does that mean?
We are not real comedians. You are not a
real audience.
What does that mean? Nobody's charging
you a cover, so lower your expectations.
This is an open mic. What you came to is
free comedy. You're going to see some
awesome moments. You're probably going
to see some bad moments, too. That's
kind of a part of being on the cutting
edge of things. You're there for the
successes. You're there for the
failures. You're on you're on the train
for the ride. Get ready to go for it. Uh
tonight's theme, every week we do a
theme. Tonight's theme is drunks. Uh
someone suggested drunk uncles. Felt
like that was a little too specific, so
we're just saying drunk family members
in general, but drunks is such a fun
name that that's what we're going with.
Um if you don't have the drunk in your
family,
>> chances are it's you. It's very
possible. Check with your uh nephews and
nieces. Um I remember my niece told me
recently, she just turned 16. She was
like, "Hey, I was at a party and they
were smoking weed." And I was like, "Oh,
cool." And she's like, "No." I was like,
"Oh, not cool." She's like, "I could
tell they were smoking weed when I
walked in there and I was like, "This
room smells like Uncle Chino."
And then she put two and two together
and found out that I've been the cool
uncle all along. That's how you That's
how you find out. She thought I was the
angry uncle until she's like, "You're
not the angry uncle." I was like, "I
just did that so you would stay away."
Um, so we're doing jokes about drunk
family. Um, or whatever substance you
want to talk about your family being on.
Just remember what you're saying is
being live streamed currently. We do
have a YouTube channel, comedy
simulator. Currently streaming live. How
many viewers we got right now? Only 66
currently, but last week we had 42K tune
in on us. So yeah, every week it's got a
pretty cool number. The the there's
there's comments comedians can see from
here, audience members, if you want to
watch it, uh you can check from our
channel. We don't post we don't put them
live on the screen anymore because they
were pretty offensive. But if you like
your comedy, Super Spicy, go ahead and
watch the live stream on your YouTube on
your phone as we do this so that you can
see the show within the show. It's very
Shakespearean. It's unlike any other
comedy experience that you've ever been
a part of. And online audience, thanks
for tuning in. Appreciate you guys. Uh,
a lot of you from Australia, Britain,
America, and uh, where else they uh,
Usbekiststan, something like that.
Apparently, I look Kazak. Uh, so they're
like, "Yeah, we we [ __ ] with that. They
like seeing themselves on screen." I'm
happy to be a part of that. U,, thanks
for checking in. They're normally
commenting. I normally give hot sauce to
some of the best comic uh, comments on
the stream. And you know what? Let's do
that tonight. If you live in America and
you lay down some fire in the comment
section, I might just send you a
four-pack of hot sauce. There we go. And
that brings us up to our next point.
Tonight's sponsor of the show is High
Spice Hot Sauce.
That's right. Viewers can check out our
website, highspice.com, and type in coms
sim 10 for 10% off of their online
order. But in house today, audience
member of the night, you will win a free
bottle of ice spice hot sauce. Locally
grown, handcrafted. I can tell you it's
handcrafted cuz it's my hands that
crafted it. That's right. My DNA might
be traced in there. My blood, sweat, and
tears. Not all of those things at once,
but one of those three definitely
possible. If you want my hands in your
mouth, this is the only way to get it.
>> We're going to work on these
catchphrases. They don't sound
appetizing, but I have two different
sauces that come in our holographic
labels. Here, get a zoom of this. This
guy, we got our phenomena.
It's made specifically for fur. Great
mushroom flavors there. And we have the
the kalanji malange, a [snorts]
Indian style curry sauce. Both of a good
medium high heat. So, if you're good,
you could win this. What is audience
member of the night? quality level
reach. Be here and stay here and be
here. That's all. Hey, if you showed up
for the class, you get a C. That's how
it works. We're like remedial math.
We're just happy you showed up. [ __ ]
I'm going to teach you how to count with
change. That's how it works. No. All
right. Um, I explain the rules. I
explain how it starts. All the comics
get 5 minute sets. We have a whole list
of comics tonight. If you guys want to
get up, we have a list right here
available. Early and late spots
available. Are we ready to begin the
comedy simulator? Woo!
>> Let's do it. Begin simulation.
Um, so I didn't really have a lot of uh
drunks in my life because my family were
straight up criminals on one side. Um,
I didn't have a drunk. I had a a methal.
Do you know what what
>> I had?
>> All right. All right. [laughter]
If they did any time at Red Roof on
Wahoo, our uncles are brothers. I
guarantee it, bro. He was cellmate's
cousin. I guarantee it. Uh, no, I have I
I'll never forget one time I didn't see
my uncle's and my one aunt Denise I I
didn't see my uncles for years and uh
they were coming in for a visit and my
parents were nervous. And I was like,
why are you guys so nervous? And they're
like,
you don't understand. They I'll use my
real name. Like, you don't understand,
Curtis. Your family isn't Well, they're
not all like us. And my dad was like
trying to explain that there's like
different types of Hawaiians
and he's like I went to the Air Force. I
mean, you know, but the we're from Khi.
You got to understand, boy.
Trying to level with me like, oh, I'm
starting to understand, you know. And
then uh they show up in a Winnebago.
Now, they weren't the Partridge family.
They were not on tour playing bars
across America. I'd never seen my uncle
in a Winnebago before. He gets out.
like, "Hey, what's up, BOY? LONG TIME NO
SEE." HEY, GET INSIDE the get inside the
van. Where you going? I'm like, "Where
you going?" He's like, "What you like
do? What you like do?" And I was I was I
was living in Southern California at the
time. They're from Vegas. And I was
like, "I don't know. I want to go play
laser tag and eat chili fries." He's
like, "Get in. We going." We went to
laser tag. We started playing. And he's
just swiping the credit card left and
right. And my dad's just standing there
like sweating. I'm like, "What's what,
Dad? Why are you so nervous? Just play
some laser tag." He's like, "Oh,
whatever." So, we're playing laser tag.
We're eating chili cheese fries. We're
talking about getting ice cream. We're
going all these different places. And
then like my dad finally leveled with
me. I was like, "Dad, how come we don't
hang out with this uncle more? I love
him so much." He's like, "Because that's
not his money." You
My uncle went back to prison a month
later and I haven't seen him in 25
years. That's
That's my drunks. Your Your drunks don't
party like my drunks. Uh, my parents, my
parents though, they like to tie one on.
Um, I told this story last week, but
it's a pretty new audience. I'll tell it
again. Um, my dad had this joke he'd
play on me every birthday. He'd be like,
"Son, your cake smells funny." And I'd
go to smell it and he'd every time three
years in a row my dad got me with this
joke. You think I would have learned,
especially in that sponge state of a
nine-year-old that I would have retained
this knowledge, but 8, nine, and 10, he
got me. until one Fourth of July, my mom
made this beautiful cake and my dad was
cutting into it and I was like, "Hey,
Dad, this cake kind of smells funny."
And he was just drunk enough. He was
like, "What? No way. It's only been out
for like 20 minutes." I'm like, "I swear
it stinks. You got to smell it." He's
like, "No way." He goes to smell it. And
in my excitement, instead of going,
[clears throat]
I WENT, "OH, YOU GET I like uppercuted
I Mortal Kombat uppercuted this cake
into my dad's face, painted them, and I
found out in that moment that drunk dad
jokes are only funny if you're the dad."
I got the ass whipping of a lifetime. On
the 4th of July, too, while fireworks
are going off, no one can hear you
scream. No [ __ ] Oh yeah,
>> you guys seem to be pulling back away
from the trauma material. I got one
worse
>> that I'm planning on telling, but you
guys seem to not have the stomach for
it. You guys okay with
>> Cuz we're going to go dark tonight. It's
a drunkle night. We're going to go dark,
right?
>> All right. All right. Check this out.
>> 12 years old.
My mom's missing for a couple days.
She ended up being at the bar for a
while bartender calls me. I have to
drive her home. I'm 12. don't know, but
I know how to drive. This is for these
scenarios. Driving home. I'm ask her
questions. She won't tell me anything
but the lyrics of Smash Mouse Allstar.
>> That must have been the last song I was
playing cuz every time my mom worries,
she's like, "Hey now,
you're an allstar.
Get your game on." I'm like, "It's been
like two days." She's like, "Get a cold
place."
Say it is colder
now. Most songs of trauma go away,
right?
Why hasn't Smash Mouse Allstar gone
away?
It had a resurgence from Shrek and then
Trump. That song will not die. I want
you to know that song is supposed to be
a joyous song, but every time I hear Hey
Now, what I really hear is hey now, and
[laughter]
I'm going to have like a freak out in
the middle of a KFC or something. like
I'm it's gonna activate me like a
sleeper cell. Anyways, if you guys don't
laugh, I'm be like, "Hey, now."
All right, you guys ready to start the
show? [cheering]
>> Let's do this. Ladies and gentlemen,
your first performer tonight uh has got
some burles shows coming up pretty soon.
I hope she
>> at least one. I hope she'll tell you
about it. At least she'll do her set.
Ladies and gentlemen, get over Miss
Abra.
[applause]
>> Hi everyone. I'm Abra. Hello there. I do
have a burlap show coming up. It is on
November 27th, the day after
Thanksgiving. It is called
Spanksgiving.
Yes, it is Black and Blue Friday. Mhm.
And it's at Pro Arts at 7:30. Tickets
are going fast. Anyway, I wanted to come
up here and say very personal and and
very specific things using good words,
but I am a part-time drunk. Okay, that's
right. I'm not professional. I'm a I'm
an enthusiastic hobbyist. Okay, so bear
with me here.
>> Oh, yeah. I'm old, too. Anyway, this has
nothing to do with the gentle,
beautiful, and sensitive crowd here
tonight. Thank you all for being human
and kind and gentle and and an easy
laugh. I am addressing the chat which
ironically isn't as full as it normally
is which is probably very good for many
reasons right now.
Yes, chat. Hi chat. I'm addressing you.
you darling group of individuals that
feel so driven to bully this
nonprofessional
bar open mic uh full of uh misfits and
mentally unstable. Yes, that's me. See?
Anyway, that's me. Um
>> we're up here. We are up here despite
our own overwhelming problems. That's
right. Hi, Dove. like failing eyesight,
Tourette's,
poor bladder control,
[snorts] as well as coping with the
crippling depression caused by the
general shittiness of reality,
pollution, corruption, greed, and all
the other problems that come from our
desensitized citizens and evil
politicians. Excuse me, sir. Excuse me,
sir. Aren't you a senator?
Oh, it's irrelevant. It's irrelevant.
We're all here doing our best right now.
Back to the chat.
>> In light of all this, I must ask, do you
also feel compelled to [ __ ] on the
Special Olympics?
Um, anyway, I mean, we're getting our
participation trophies right now just by
being here in real life doing this
general humiliation ritual. That's
right. And enjoying it. Do you heckle
the Humane Society? Or maybe you prefer
to murder puppies in your spare time.
What's really funny is that I don't read
any of it because I feel that it's
probably just a bunch of angry,
powerless people like me that need more
love and attention generally. That's why
I'm here. The truth is, if you made or
had one kind comment or one relevant
piece of advice that would hit me to my
core and make me cry because I am a
mentally unstable person. I'm a damn I'm
a damaged, sensitive [ __ ]
And you know what? I'm being as kind as
I can because the world needs more
sweetness and caring. That's right. more
laughter. Thank you. Thank you. Thank
you. That's right. [laughter]
And and that's what I'm here trying to
do. Just give a little bit of more
laughter in the world. Which reminds me,
do you know what's worse than ants in
your pants?
>> Drunkles. That's right. My name's Abra.
Good night.
[applause and cheering]
>> Keep it going, Abra. Ladies and
gentlemen,
now she hates it when the chat speaks
negatively as you can see, but uh I love
it when they talk. I I actually enjoy
it. I feel like it's like me talking to
my own family, right? Whereas it's like
this is how we talk during Thanksgiving.
Whoever gets the best roast normally
gets the biggest hug. So be mean to me.
Don't don't be mean to her. Uh but you
can be you can continue to be mean to
me. Uh so my second spot comic is
running a little late. Would anybody
else like to go in the second spot? Jump
up your spot right now. If you're last
on the list, you could could go second.
Go once. Second going twice.
>> Second go three times. All right. Sasha,
you ready?
>> Number three. Jumping up to number two.
Ladies and gentlemen, give me Sasha.
[applause]
>> Thank you.
>> I was lucky number three. Now I'm number
two. Unfortunately,
[laughter]
Anybody here visiting?
No. Okay. Well, that's good. I would
feel terrible about ruining your
vacation.
Um, so I guess I am the drunkle. I mean,
most of my family members are. I'm
really good at telling you things that
are awkward and make you feel just a
little bit icky. So, I I think I'll just
run with [snorts] that. Uh, anybody here
doing any online dating?
>> Yeah. Yeah. So, I find it works really
well for me because
it's my photos and doesn't involve me
saying anything or, you know, talking,
which tends to kind of put a damper on
things. Um, you know, did you know that
sharks have two penises? That that's the
things I like to talk about. They're not
really penises though technically. Um
they they're very phallic looking and
they are used for depositing sperm, but
they're technically claspers. So yeah.
Yeah, claspers. So that that's why it's
better to just see my photo and not talk
to me as far as making matches. I get a
lot of matches. Um I don't get a lot of
second dates. Uh, which is why I decided
last year to take a break from the apps
and have a family member set me up.
Keeping with the theme of family, uh, my
cousin's wife, uh, really lovely lady, a
doctor,
uh, you know, told me about this guy
that she met at a medical conference and
she's like, he's an anesthesiologist and
he's from South Africa. I was like,
okay, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
South Africa. So like you know like what
kind of South African? And she's like
what do you mean? And I was like well
like is he black? Is he like Zulu? She's
like no he's white. And I was like okay
so like what kind? Like you know. And
she's like I don't know what you mean.
And I'm just like you know like like the
bad kind like the Elon Musk kind like
Africans apartheid. And she's like I
don't I don't know what you mean. But
then she showed me his name and I was
like oh yeah no he's he's Dutch South
African. And so, of course, I'm thinking
to myself, you know, you know what I'm
thinking. It's it starts with arrays
with a cyst. Um, and and then I thought
to myself, you know, shame on you. You
know, the whole point of trying to date
is keeping an open mind and not, you
know, you're the one who's being a
racist. You just assume that he's like
that because he's white and of Dutch
descent. He might not be. Charlie's
therein is Dutch South African. Everyone
says she's lovely. he could be the boy
Charlie Sarin. Like, you know, keep an
[ __ ] open mind. So, I'm like, "Yeah,
you know what? Le let's do it." And
she's like, "Yeah, he likes a hike. You
like to hike. We'll all go on a hike."
And I'm like, "Yeah, that sounds really
good." And so, then I get to work one
day and everybody is talking about like,
"Did you hear about this? Did you guys
hear about this?" Um, this this
anesthesiologist
uh from Maui
or like who lives on Maui. Uh he he he
went over to Wahoo with his wife and he
he pushed her off the poly. Like he
[ __ ] pushed her off a cliff. I was
like, "What the fuck?" And so then, you
know, I say to my cousin's wife, I'm
like, "Oh, that's so funny cuz like you
know, you know anesthesiologist likes to
go hiking." And she's like, "It's him."
And I was like, "What?" Like, "You're
joking. You're joking." She's like, "No,
no, it's him." I was like, "Oh my
[ __ ] god. Can you believe this guy
was married?" H just terrible, terrible.
Uh but also like the fact that he, you
know, attempted to murder his wife. Uh
[laughter]
[gasps] so yeah, it turned out that uh
he was married with kids. Uh none of
this he revealed to my cousin's wife
obviously and he, you know, had planned
this whole thing. I mean, he's obviously
planning to be sk single to his credit.
Uh but
uh yeah, so his last text to her, my
cousin's wife, uh was I can't wait to go
hiking with you. So like I don't know if
he like just has a kink for pushing
women off of cliffs and he was planning
to push both of us off the cliff or you
know I really don't know. I mean the
thing the thing about it is this is the
one situation where it would have been
better if he were a racist. Like I'm
never going to say that again. Like I
would never want my date to be a racist,
but in this case it would have been
better if he were racist. So you know he
is in prison now and I am back on the
apps and you know it's going well. I'm
getting some world class dick pics. So
thank you very much.
[applause]
Keep going, Sasha. Ladies and gentlemen,
I never loots in the chat said that he
did it all for you. [laughter]
Uh, by the way, once again, you can
follow our YouTube channel currently uh
on the stream. Uh, we've had a couple
people buy some hot sauce already, too.
So, thanks to you. Shout out. All right,
moving right [snorts] along, ladies and
gentlemen. Your next comment coming up
to the stage. Uh, so we've been having
an online signup list and comedians,
sorry if there's a back and forth of uh
who doesn't know where they are. If you
don't know where your spot is on the
list, just come talk to me. Ladies and
gentlemen, coming to the stage, one of
my favorites, a westsider that moved to
Keyhand is now back on the west side.
Keep it over Corki Gardener.
[applause]
I'll put your private
Hey guys. Um, my name's Corky. You
probably heard of me. You come here
sometimes.
>> Corky's name joking the game. And I'm
really excited about this because I'm
taking the topic to mean anything weird
about your family,
>> right?
>> Chino.
>> Chino. Is it just like any crazy weird
stuff about your family?
>> Yeah, like drunk drunk family.
>> Drunk family stuff. Um, my dad was a a
scam artist and he was married nine
times.
Nine times. My mom is the eighth wife
and I'm his second batch of kids. Uh,
let me see. I met him because my mom was
engaged to marry my uncle and uh she he
invited him down to get the blessing.
[laughter]
Don't do that.
He said, "She looks good to me.
[laughter]
What's no no laughing? Dan, is that
funny? No.
>> I'm having a I'm out on a limb here,
Chino.
>> Anyhow, is anybody judging me right now?
No.
>> Okay, good. So, the guy, my dad's like,
uncle's like, "Hey, come see my wife.
She's really cool. I want to marry this
lady." And when he got there, she was so
high. My uncle's like, "Get her out of
the house." And and he got her in the
car and took her on a trip to uh Big Su
and they fell in love. [laughter]
Isn't that cute?
>> But I was really close to being my own
cousin. [laughter]
That's weird, huh? So, I met my uncle.
Whenever I talked to my uncle, it was
kind of weird, you know? He the dad I'm
like dad/ uncle pops.
But, but we had a good time. And my mom
was like a go-go dancer and my dad was a
bank robber. Like, I couldn't say that
because statute of limitations.
Uh, but now I can. So, I'm going to tell
you what happened. Um, my dad went and
he went to the he started his own bank
and he got people to donate money to the
bank cuz it was gardener savings and
loan, right? And then he took
everybody's money and he spent it,
[laughter]
you know, was that too much?
>> Looks like a real bank.
>> And then and then he had to leave town
and change his name and live in
Kennyport, Maryland. And he worked at a
candle factory. So that's before I met
him. Anyhow, he was wild. Then he had to
take his kids and give them to his
sister. And then he had to steal a car
and a car he went and he took a car from
a car dealership and said he's taking it
on a test drive and he drove it from
California to Maine.
And when it broke down, he dressed up
like the mechanic
[laughter]
and he got his keys back and he stole
the car.
A legend. And then he went and got his
kids back. [laughter] And then he went
to back to the courthouse and to turn
himself in. And he said, "I am
gardener." And they said, "Oh, you're
gardener. The guy on your case killed
himself
[laughter]
and we want to get these files out of
here." So, we shred all the files and
they got off the case and they let him
go. That's my dad.
[cheering]
>> All right, I think I said enough.
>> I'm going to go now.
>> Thank you.
[applause]
>> The fruit of his loins. Corky Garner.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I love how she said that he had nine
wives and then he he she she was like,
"Yeah, he was a candle dipper." He's
like, "Yeah, he sure was.
That wick is wet." All right.
>> Oh my god.
>> Oh, was that?
>> Really? Do you not know what husbands do
with their wives? Are we uh playing koi
here? Okay. All right, then.
>> Wax.
>> They wax. Yeah, they wax. They All
right. Actually, I don't know what
people do with their wives. I'm a 40
40-year-old wifeless man. What? What?
What? What do they do?
>> I don't know, but they look very
unhappy. All right, [laughter] we're
going to keep this moving. We got plenty
of comics. Who's up next? Oh, that's
right. You are. Ladies and gentlemen, uh
oh, before before I bring him up, I just
want to say Corky Gardner is now hosting
dinners for one at her house. Uh
[laughter]
you can make your reser I'm not joking.
You can make your reservations. It can
include a comedy performance or a
concert or just dinner where she won't
say anything to you. And
>> and I've never been more charmed
[clears throat] by executive private
chef proposition than that. Just like I
don't have to talk. So Chef Corki
>> [applause]
>> uh will cook for you.
Her menu is not selective. No
substitutions. No no allergies. We're
going for it. All right. Just just eat
it. All right, ladies and gentlemen,
coming to the stage right now, a
comedian who's selling cookies for his
daughter. If you like cookies, TALK TO
HER. GET OVER STEVIE.
[applause]
>> All right, thank you, Chino. Let's keep
going for Chino and Pame Coffee Bar for
keeping this thing going. We're getting
some rain and it doesn't seem to be
hurricane related, so that's pretty
awesome.
>> Hooray. So, uh, Corki, that does sound
like a good idea. I'll take a dinner.
All right.
>> Do I Can I get comedy, music, and a
conversation?
>> 500 bucks.
>> [ __ ] Never mind. I'm out.
>> All right. Never mind. What if I cook
for you?
>> Call it a draw.
>> Call it a draw. All right. Good. That's
That's my price frame. Um, yeah. So, uh,
Corki, your dad was a crook. Um, my
uncle was a well, he was a crook by the
government standards.
So he started a uh bartering system in
the community and he got arrested for
that for tax evasion evidently.
>> Yeah. Criminality, I know, but like in a
good way. So he's kind of like a kind of
like a Robin Hood of sorts. But um also
because of him and his disdain for the
government. I found out when I was at
least 10 or maybe even younger that um
the government is controlled by
reptilians.
That was a long time ago. So he was way
early on the game, you know. So, he
didn't want the reptiles to get that
money. So, hey, barter your way away.
You know, chicken for a cow.
I don't know.
But, um,
yeah, he was also uh like he he was a
bit of a drunk. Had a bit of a you know,
he could drink. And when he he used to
work uh at a restaurant and he played
for a softball team and evidently he got
really drunk uh one night and uh got
fired and kicked off the team at the
same time. But he was really good. So
the other restaurant quick put him in
the line. So he just switched teams and
restaurants, you know, but he did get
fired from that cuz he did wind up
sleeping with the owner's wife. So
>> home run.
Good job.
Um, let's see. Uh, he was drunk during
his baby's birth.
>> Um, yeah. So, it's kind of bad evidently
to, uh, be so drunk that you put your
wife into labor because she's upset.
Yeah, that's one way to, you know, get
the baby to come. So, the baby came out.
They both puked and passed out. So, you
know, like father like daughter.
That's good.
Um, now he has been he's been dead for
way over 10 years now. Um, and he was
one of those conspiracy guys. So,
they're still looking for the gold
that's all over his property. It's it's
there. All right. I'm Dan Stevie. That's
my time.
[applause]
>> Dan Stevie ain't no snitch. Get up. Man,
Stevie, ladies and gentlemen, [applause]
outing no family members there. Um, all
right. Coming up next to the stage,
ladies and gentlemen, this next comic uh
runs the Tuesday night mic in Kihei. If
this isn't enough open mic comedy for
you, you can get more on a Tuesday night
in Kihei and vibe. Ladies and gentlemen,
one, the only Morgan Tasian.
[applause]
>> Hello. Aloha everybody. Welcome to
National Pa's
night.
Um
I had this thought on the way over here.
Uh Trumple like a uncle who loves or
hates Donald Trump depending who he's
talking to.
He's kind of Yeah, exactly. He's He's
just kind of on both sides, you know. He
can argue about anything. Just tell him
what side. Uh, meanwhile, shout out to
Dan. You know, they say that 99%
of all Dans are not actually the man,
>> but but this guy right here.
>> Let me tell you,
>> that was close.
>> He is the man. Let me tell you. Okay, so
we got that out of the way.
Conspiracy theories.
I had an uncle who's a real good
conspiracy theorist. But uh three
conspiracy theorists walk into a bar.
That can't be a coincidence.
No, it can't. U you know there's a lot.
Are you v vaccinated by the way for co
sir?
>> He is. He is good man. I know. I've had
uh vaccine hesitancy ever since the
booster gave my girlfriend chlamyia.
I'm just kidding. It was her best
friend, too. I mean, what a coincidence.
Uh no. Um
yeah. No, but uh but one of my favorite
conspiracy theories has to be the one
that just we just had the anniversary
for 25 years. Can't believe it's been
that long. 911.
And what's crazy about 911 that you know
the greatest conspiracy is is that it
was an inside job.
And
I think it's kind of kind of interesting
like could you imagine
seven years later Osama bin Laden
just put yourself in his sandals for a
minute.
He's still alive, but he's been laying
low and he wants to see what the world
is saying about 911. So, he checks in
the YouTube chat
and he sees that the internet
not giving him credit for 9/11,
the greatest terrorist attack on
Americans in all of history. And they're
like, "Nah, it wasn't him, man. It was
the CIA. It was the, you know, it was
the government. They did it. It was the
There was a lot of other police people
doing it, you know, and and it's like
he's online and he's looking, he's got
to have like a fake name. And he's on
the YouTube chats and there's somebody
going, "Well, the, you know, the
airplane fuel doesn't melt steel."
And he's like, "Well, it it does
actually." You know, he's like chatting
in. He's like, "It does melt steel. It
doesn't have to melt steel. It just
needs to bend it a little bit.
>> No. Okay. Going somewhere else. Anyway,
you know, um
>> I know. Yeah, Flat Earth's uh Uncle
Flatter. That That's what I'm talking
about. Moving on. Um No. Yeah. The
world's a crazy place right now. I uh
Hey, hey, don't shoot the messenger.
I just wanted to get in my Charlie Kirk
joke uh before the time ran out. Um um
[ __ ]
>> Oh yeah. My impression of the Michelin
man.
I just flew in from Detroit
and boy are my arms tires.
Boy are my arms tires. [laughter]
Oh my god. No. Uh one more. Uh let's
see. My my uncle No, he did actually. He
smoked a lot and um he smoked actually
two packs a day for 40 years
and then he died of a noose.
I'm just kidding. He shot himself 9 9 mm
Beretta.
A really dumb way to die. [singing]
[applause]
Morganation, ladies and gentlemen. Um,
>> I don't like he that he referred to 911
as the single greatest terrorist attack.
I don't like that terminology.
>> Cuz that sounds like a sporting event,
right?
And we're just on the wrong team.
Cuz we think of it as like, oh yeah, we
remember that terrible moment. But that
means anybody on the terrorist team was
like, "Shit, remember that one time
where we actually did it?" Like, "Oh,
no. I don't like thinking that at all. I
don't like that." Change your gnome and
clature. Morgan, say something like the
single most
>> prolific. I like prolific.
>> Actually, we shouldn't like it. I I'll
think about that. All right. Uh, ladies
and gentlemen, coming up next to the
stage, coming off of a super successful
show last night at Pro Art Theater, who
went to that show?
[applause and cheering]
>> I heard it was banging. If you guys
weren't there, you missed it. There's
another one coming up soon. What are we
talking about? Ladies and gentlemen,
give her Shah Nelson.
[applause]
>> What up?
My name is Shane Nelson and tonight is
uncle night. Um, we're going to start
off. Who here is a parent? Make some
noise if you have kids.
>> Now, make some noise if you're an aunt
or an uncle.
Woo! [cheering] Woo!
>> It's louder, right? And that's because
being a parent sucks, dude. I am a
millennial. I was born in the '9s. And
millennials, we're not having kids cuz
it sucks being a parent. Like back in
the day, if you had a kid and your kid
was [ __ ] off, he if he was being a
little maf, you could hit them, right?
>> Nowadays, you can't hit your kids. If
you hit your kids, they hate your kids.
But as an uncle, I can hit my nephew.
What's he going to do? tell his dad.
>> You know whose dad is? My brother. I've
been fighting that [ __ ] for 34 years. I
will fight that [ __ ] again. Go ahead,
tell your dad. I'm ready. I want that.
Thank you.
My nephew, he is cute. Uh he's 12 years
old and whenever I call [clears throat]
him, he's always so excited. He'll
answer the phone. He'll like, "Hello."
He sounds a lot like Mickey Mouse. She's
very supportive and there's lots of
woohoo on the phone. It's a good phone
call. And tonight's about drunkles. Is
that the word? Drunk.
Um, so the last time I went to visit my
nephew, his name is Stu. He lives in
Minnesota and he I hope he's not
watching this. Um, I went there for
Thanksgiving and I ate half a duck. And
if you ever eat half a duck, you kind of
feel drunk. If you've ever eaten half a
duck, you don't feel good. And uh while
I was staying with my my nephew, I was
sleeping in his bed. He was sleeping on
the couch. And I was drunk on duck and I
uh I [ __ ] his bed.
I pooped a 12-year-old's bed
in the morning. He's like, "How'd you
sleep?" And I was like, "Great."
I can't tell him, dude. He can't know.
I I went to a family reunion in
Minnesota one time and half my family is
liberal and half my family is
conservative and it was so cool to see
like the change in the conservatives in
my family were like during co they were
so against the mask right I can't wear a
mask I can't breathe in the mask [ __ ] I
[ __ ] this up I think already
>> I'm leaving it um at that family reunion
I I saw my aunt and She told me that my
uh one of my nephews has cancer and he
was given a year to live.
And uh what one thing he wanted to do
before he died is he wanted to try magic
mushrooms. And she's like, "Can you get
your your nephew some magic mushrooms?"
And he was 15 years old at the time. And
like I've sold drugs to kids, right?
I haven't. I wouldn't. But
is that is that convincing if you guys
were a jury?
I was like, maybe I should make an
exception though. He has like a year to
live. And by raise of hands, if there
was a child that's 15 years old, he has
one year to live and he wanted to try
magic mushrooms. Is it okay to give him
magic mushrooms? Raise your hand if it's
a yes. [applause]
>> I think so. Cuz like life is short.
Experience it. We don't know if we get a
second round, right? But now, let's say
he he changes his make a wish and he's
like, "You know what? I'm 15. I have a
year to live. I've never had sex."
Is it okay to buy a 15year-old that has
one year to live a prostitute?
[applause]
Sex is one of the greatest things in
life, right? Like, imagine dying of
never having sex, dude.
>> Yeah. He's 15 years old, but that's like
40 in cancer years, right?
who who raised their hand for the find a
prostitute just so I can see.
>> Okay, miss [laughter] this.
>> Let's say he changes his wish one more
time. He's like, I'm 15. I have a year
to live. My one wish in this world is to
have sex with you.
>> No. And that's the correct answer. I'm
Chris Hansen.
Walked right into that one. Why'd you
bring so much pizza and condoms?
>> [laughter]
>> No, that is the right answer cuz yeah,
he's 15. Uh, but that's like 80 years
prison years for you, right?
>> No, but you Oh, yeah, for me. But you
can find an 18year-old prostitute.
>> Whoa. Whoa. Where?
>> Well, [laughter]
>> yeah. What's her number? Where? Where is
she? How much is she? [laughter]
He's budging.
>> Does anyone have any questions for me?
[laughter]
>> This is the point of the show where I
take questions.
>> Yes, Miss your girlfriend instead of the
prostitute.
>> You're going to have to say that again.
>> Why didn't you choose your girlfriend
instead of the prostitute?
>> Can you translate for me, sir?
>> Oh, my girlfriend. Like, I have a
girlfriend.
>> Good one. You should be up here telling
jokes.
I uh
>> I wrote this joke three years ago.
>> He died a virgin, dude. That's [ __ ]
sad.
>> Any more questions before I leave?
Actually, I have to go catch a bus.
>> Okay, goodbye. My name is Shane Nelson.
Aloha.
[applause]
>> Making you question your morals. the
Jane Nelson. Ladies and gentlemen,
>> yes, that apprehension is what that
deserves. You're absolutely right.
You're good people. Good people. All
right. Coming up next to the stage, the
co-producer of last night's show. It's
not at all weird that they both came in
wearing sunglasses looking exactly like
each other. You be the judge. Ladies and
gentlemen, coming up to the stage, Ger
Jackson. Bye-bye.
I uh I I grew up in New Hampshire with a
dad that does construction.
All I knew were drunkles, guys. It's
literally the only thing they make out
there. My uh
>> my dad my dad was an alcoholic and uh he
uh he actually drank enough spiced rum
while trying to make me
>> that I came out looking like Captain
Morgan.
>> I guess
Shane came first, I guess. I don't know.
>> My uh my dad, he drank a lot like
growing up and stuff. And my uh my
birthday is like the end of March, so
sometimes it falls on Easter. And uh if
you guys also had a alcoholic
parent, you probably also went through a
divorce. So they uh I had like, you
know, two birthday dinners. My dad
picked me up from Easter. We went to a
Chinese restaurant cuz that's all that
was open.
And uh he he was ordering and to end it,
he uh he looked at this lady and he
said, "And uh Paul Frive
in that exact voice." And my head
immediately popped up like, "Yo, dude,
we got to come back here eventually."
And he just looked back at me like a dog
that just pooped the carpet.
It's like, "Dude, I I didn't mean to,
>> but that's, you know, it's What happens
when you have a construction working dad
in New England?
>> My uh my other my uncle
I I get the like love to embarrass the
people I'm close to from my family.
Like my my uncle would come down from
Maine and anytime he would he would
always walk me out to the bus
with his pants at his nipples on
purpose.
Like there's just an old moose knuckle
walking me.
All right, I guess hate moose knuckles.
All right, what is he going to do after
that?
I uh I'm kind of the drunkle now. You
know, my my good friend has he just had
his second kid
and uh I I remember talking to my dad
when he had his first kid and I was
like, "Yo, dude, it's crazy that like my
friends are having kids now. Can you
imagine me having a kid?" And his
immediate answer was, "No."
Dad has a lot of faith in me.
You guys hate my family apparently.
>> It's called disdain.
>> Disdain. That's I mean I hope they don't
disdain my family. That's a little
rough.
It's a lot worse than hating, I think,
at this point.
But no, I'm I'm always on her side.
It's a lot of fun.
And it's you just figure out how to
basically piss off your friend using his
own child. It's a great time.
All right, I'm going to do one more and
then let me get the [ __ ] out of here.
I uh it it is a lot different, you know,
like when you're a you're a parent,
you're like, "Oh, I will protect this
kid at any cost and do anything."
Yeah.
>> But then if you're
>> an uncle to the kid, you're like, "Oh,
like this is just a
>> tiny little idiot right now. This is
>> my friend. This is great." Like you just
realize like, "Oh, dude." Like every
horrible, horrible person throughout
history
was just a tiny little idiot at one
point. She still might turn out that
way. I'm her uncle. All right, guys. I'm
Jackson Babine.
Yeah. Have a good night. [applause]
>> Jackson Bayine, ladies and gentlemen.
Big difference from last night's
audience, huh? Yeah. Shell shot.
>> He also partied really hard after that
show, so I'm sure he's got a little
hangover going on, too. He wasn't given
100 either. It's okay. Don't worry about
it. It's a Monday. All right. Uh, coming
up next to the stage, ladies and
gentlemen, has become a bit of a uh a
bit of a circus act here at the Comedy
Simulator. Um, his comedy does something
weird to my brain and is probably going
to do the same thing to you guys. I have
no idea how else to explain him other
than the one and only. We gave him a
name, Dumpster Danny. Ladies and
gentlemen, Dumpster Danny.
[applause]
How we doing tonight?
>> My name is Danny and it is good to be
back.
So, I was a big alcoholic back in my
day. I started drinking at the age 10. I
read my first porn magazine at age seven
and lost my virginity at age 13. And now
here I am today.
Now, as an alcoholic, I had a lot of
regrets. So, here's a few things of what
not to do when you drink. Number one, if
it's ever like very hot outside and
you're trying to figure out how to make
your house more cooler, never ever put a
block of dry ice in front of your fan.
It may seem like a good idea at first,
but what you're really doing is you're
allowing a lot of carbon dioxide to flow
through your house, and eventually
you'll suffocate and die. Not not right
away. Not right away, but eventually
you'll suffer a canned diet. I came very
close on that one.
Number two, how many weightlifterss do
we got here? Anybody here lift weights?
>> Okay. Now, how many people here use
supplements like creatine? I'm a
creatine guy. I like to use creatine.
>> Now, when you use creatine, you're
supposed to mix it with like juice and
water. You're not supposed to smoke the
[ __ ] because if you smoke the [ __ ] the
only thing that's going to happen,
you're going to get very sick to your
stomach and you're going to puke in the
toilet for about a few hours. So, let's
not do that [ __ ] neither.
And number three, number three, never
ever play with an Ouija board by
yourself at an old Confederate soldier
cemetery,
especially at night. The only thing
that's going to happen is they're going
to attract a lot of evil spirits to you
and eventually you're going to need
about three years of therapy. So, let's
not do that [ __ ] neither.
>> So, after high after high school, I
always wanted to go to a clown college.
>> It's just too bad there was no clown
colleges available after high school.
Now, back in the '9s, clown colleges
were like [ __ ] booming everywhere. No
[ __ ] I'm telling you, it was actually
at one time it was more harder to get
into a clown college than a Harvard
University. And that's true [ __ ] You
guys can Google that all you want.
That's right, folks. There's nothing
wrong with being a professional clown.
They'll teach you how to juggle in one
hand and finger [ __ ] in the other.
So, how many ladies here tonight have
ever been like in a real [ __ ] up
relationship?
>> Now, you know what your problem is,
ladies? You always end up with the guy
that you got to tell twice to do
something. Now, me on the other hand, I
don't mind at all being the [ __ ] of the
relationship.
I'm totally fine with that. I'll even do
things for you that you don't want me to
do. Your breakfast is on the counter,
dear, and I just iron your dress.
Remember, folks, a relationship isn't
just about sex, drugs, and furniture.
It's also a business.
a business that also besides court dates
and lawyers.
And when [ __ ] doesn't go right in court,
people come up missing.
What exactly am I talking about? I do
not know.
[laughter]
>> So, I still haven't received my $5,000
from Donald Trump yet.
>> And I had a I had a lot a lot of plans
for that money, too. You know, I had a
lot of plans. I was going to buy my cat
a new cap box, but a good cap box, you
know, one of those cap boxes that clean
themselves and all the [ __ ] lights
light up and [ __ ] My cat would have
loved that one.
Maybe a few tickets to the Miley Cyrus
concert.
A couple pyote plants for the house
and a brand new assassination rifle. I
mean, hunting rifle. Hunting rifle. Holy
[ __ ] Did I say assassination rifle? We
could probably delete that one. We don't
got to put that one. We're not [ __ ]
live streaming this, are we?
>> Oh, [ __ ] FBI will be looking for me for
sure.
>> All right, folks. That's all I got.
Thank you.
[applause]
>> Give him Dumpster Danny. Ladies and
gentlemen,
[applause]
>> with a name like Dumpster Danny, he
never disappoints. Uh, this mic is so
unhinged. I love I love I love this. By
the way, Cooking with Corki, Chef Corky
Gardner gave me a piece of chocolate
cake. One of the desserts that you can
expect [laughter] at her cooking for
one. How many courses is the meal,
Corki?
>> Two. It's a two course meal, but the
portions, what are the portions like,
Corki?
>> Huge.
>> The portions are huge. You're You're
going to get an entire box of cake. It
looks like served to you on the box
itself. I don't know if you can tell.
She gave me a piece of cake on a piece
of cardboard.
That is the Corky way. I appreciate the
craftsmanship, Corky. I'm gonna eat this
right now. Ladies and gentlemen, come to
the stage. Comedian uh uh immigrant and
now father added to the list. Get over
Bashar.
[applause]
>> All right, keep it going for Chino guys.
I am all of those things combined.
So, God help you. I actually have a
drunk uncle myself. Um, his name in
Arabic, it's Sad, which means uh trutht
teller. He was so charismatic.
Uh, he conned my father with all of his
life savings. Okay? And uh he didn't
just skip town, he skipped country. He
went and lived in Iran out of all
places. So, good luck to my father. He
has never got his money back. Uh, but I
still like my uncle somehow. I don't
know why he got me. I recently became a
father. Give it up guys.
3 [applause] weeks in to be exact. And
people ask me how is it like? And u I'm
like don't do it. Okay.
I think I think it's a it's a conspiracy
done by Big Baby
trying to get us all to have more
babies. Um
yeah, it is it is awesome. It is awesome
just spending time with the little one.
Um what happened to conspiracies though,
right? Like there used to be some
conspiracies where like I believed in
and everybody else didn't and it kind of
honestly made me feel a bit superior,
right? Like the 911, the MK Ultra, the
Epstein file
is files, right? But now we all kind of
know that [ __ ] is true.
>> Are there any new conspiracies now? Is
there anything that like we don't
believe in?
>> Clown school.
>> What is it?
>> Clown school. Good one. Is there a clown
school? We There's There's few of us
here. So, I guess there is, right?
You're you're learning right now.
>> Say that again.
>> Bears.
>> Yep.
>> Bernstein.
Amanda.
>> Okay. All right, guys. Let's let's chill
out on the news. See?
>> See, but it seems like all these
conspiracies
have one common denominator
that we can trace him back to.
>> Okay. All right. Like the 911. Who did
the 911 after all?
>> Charlie.
>> We can't say it. Okay.
>> Right. There's so many things so many
things and I'm here to tell you who it
is and I'm I'm tired of it. Okay,
Filipinos. Okay,
I'm tired of Filipinos. They are too
likable.
Okay, I can't stand them.
What else are we talking about? We're
talking about Donald Trump. Anybody here
voted for Donald Trump?
Yeah,
Samly, I believe you. I know you come in
sweet, but you're a closeted Trump voter
just like myself. Okay.
>> I know. I know. Hey.
Um, but you know, you got a lot of
people with Trump, they voted for him.
We're like, we want somebody that runs
the country like a business, right? We
know we want a man that runs it like a
business. We're like, yeah, like his
business. Okay, this [ __ ] is
running to the country into the ground.
We're about to bankrupt
any moment now. And there's there's
actually a fact there because his
daughter is buying an island uh in a
whole another country. Okay, that should
tell you a lot about the stock of your
own rulings where you got it happening.
Okay, this is kind of becoming more of a
um
a hate speech that needs to be
contained.
than an actual.
Okay, what else did I have for you guys?
We talked about conspiracies, talked
about baby stuff. Um, yeah, you know,
the whole thing with babies is like so
many red flags in this relationship,
right? Like we still putting up with it.
There's no giving back on the side of
the baby. I have to do everything. So, I
went ahead and just opened a few credit
cards in my baby's name. Okay. Just in
case if you don't pay me back, you're
going to have to deal with Bank of
America. Okay.
Um
All right. One problem though. I am
Iraqi. Okay. Now, that's not the
problem. If you if you knod it, if you
knod it, you're racist. No. The problem
is my baby's white. Okay. And I don't
know how to get over [laughter] [ __ ]
That is That is true. I showed my baby
to my mother and she's like, "That is a
white baby, son. What has happened to
you?" Okay. Um [laughter] All right.
Well, now that everybody's on board on
disliking this Iraqi, um we're going to
keep it going to the next comic. You
guys keep it going for your host, Gino.
[applause]
>> For sure, ladies and gentlemen. Keep it
going for him.
Hey, the white baby's your fault. You
prayed for weeks to have You're like,
"Please, please give my baby a better
life." And now you're upset. No.
>> Oh, I see all the people not laughing.
That's all the white people. That's
right. It feels weird on that side of
the privilege, doesn't it? Yeah.
>> I'm half, so I get to ride both sides.
It's wonderful. The the the racial
>> discre What was that?
>> Are you a
>> kha'? I I could be. I could be. I'm a
child of the world. I got a passport to
anywhere. Look at this face. I can go in
some middle some Middle Eastern
countries, right? Somebody with this
would pass.
>> No. [ __ ] No. No. I'm getting stoned.
Yeah, for sure. Not the way I get stoned
out here either. I definitely All right,
ladies and gentlemen. Uh, I'm going to
walk around with a tip bucket in a
second. If you guys thought I got a
little extra cash to throw the
production, we appreciate it. If you
don't, you will not be qualified to be
the audience member of the night. No,
I'm just joking. We don't lure it over
you like that. But, uh, it does
appreciate it. But coming to the stage,
probably the uh the most quafted hair of
the evening, ladies and gentlemen, the
one and only Joel Huitt.
[applause]
That's incredible. Uh congratulations,
Bashar. That's incredible. Fatherhood.
Everybody give it up for Bashar's Middle
Eastern baby. That's awesome. [applause]
That's great. Biracial love. That's
great.
>> I love your hair.
>> Thank you. Um we all know an uncle here
on Maui. You know what I mean? I run
into a bunch of uncles at the beach.
More often than not, they'll walk up to
me. They'll be like, "Oh, nephew. Why
you like polo?" And they'll try to sell
me weed, right? And I'll end up giving
them some of my weed. And about 30
minutes later, they'll come back to buy
some more from me. You know what I mean?
>> Yeah. One uncle was so thankful for the
weed that I sold him one time, he took
me to church. Took me to the Samoan
church. Now, I'm a white boy from the
Southeast, and I'm the son of a
preacher, man. So, I was putting the
howle and hallelujah that day. Come on
now. All right, that's a medium life.
Take it.
Um, let's see here. Uh,
my dad is a is a pastor and my uncle is
a chef. They're brothers. [snorts]
Uh, my uncle's also a Grateful Dead fan,
so they kind of went very different
directions in life. The pastor uncle or
the
>> They both went very different
directions.
>> My uncle. My uncle.
>> No, his dad.
>> Yeah, one is my It's not how that works.
His brother is my father. That's how
that works. It's uncle's theme. I don't
know if you got the memo. Um but yeah,
no, my uncle was a Grateful Dead fan.
And uh whenever I drink with my uncle,
it's kind of an unusual experience. My
dad doesn't drink. And uh when I drink
with my uncle, he's like, "Man, I knew
your dad when he was cool. I knew your
dad when he used to [ __ ] on rival frat
house stairs. I used to know your dad
when he dated black women."
He used to tell me he used to tell me uh
[ __ ] I forgot my [ __ ] joke. Um,
yeah. He told me, "I knew your dad back
when he got a scorpion tattoo on his ass
because he thought it was hilarious."
And I asked my dad about that the other
day. I called him up. I was like, "Hey,
Dad. Uncle Steve told me that you have a
scorpion tattoo on your ass." And all my
dad said to that was is
that's hilarious. Um, so I can't confirm
or deny whether or not he actually has
it, but that's like some lore in my
family. Um, my nephew, he's going on 12
years old.
And, uh, the other day he asked me, he
goes, "Uncle Joel, why do you smell like
weed?" And I go, "You're 12 years old.
How do you know what weed smells like?"
And we kind of caught each other in a in
an awkward moment. And I said, "Man,
[ __ ] this. I want to be a good influence
on you. We're not going to do that. Do
you want to go ride our dirt bikes
without helmets on like right now?"
>> All right.
That's good. Well, that's my nephew. Um,
I have a niece. Um, she is 13 years old
and she's a joy. Um, but the other day I
watched her eat mayonnaise out of the
jar with a spoon.
>> Yep. And uh I don't know what's
happening there. I don't know what's
going wrong there. But uh while she was
doing that, she told me, "Uncle Joel,
have you ever heard of Coco the
Gorilla?" Has anybody in this room heard
of Coco the Gorilla? Yeah. For those of
you who don't know, my niece informed me
it's a gorilla that knew 500 different
words in sign language and also was an
owner of a cat. It was a whole thing.
There's a whole documentary on it. And
uh while she was sitting there eating
mayonnaise, I said, "You know, isn't it
wild to think
that Helen Keller was almost definitely
way worse at sign language than Coco the
Gorilla?
I mean, if it if a [ __ ] monkey can do
it, how hard can it be? You know what I
mean?
>> I don't know. Even Coco Gorilla knew not
to eat mayonnaise out of the jar. All
right, that's all I got. Thank you.
[applause]
>> Keep control, ladies and gentlemen.
>> What he's saying is it so easy a caveman
can do it. Uh,
>> all right. A couple people like that
joke. All right. All right. Should have
been more. Should have been more by my
count. That was pretty funny. No. All
right. So, how many comedies we got
left? We got one, two, three, four. We
got about five more comics for the night
left. If you want to get on the list,
just put your name on. We got a few more
spots left.
>> They love the comedy.
>> You heard them. No, I think they were
honking at the people in exercise wear.
I think that's what was going on. That
That was a sexual harassment. That was
not
>> That was not a tune for us. Woo! Wait,
>> you guys are conflicted. You're like,
"Do I applaud that?" Sure. That's the
answer. Whatever. Why not? All right,
ladies and gentlemen, come to the stage
right now. I forgot who I said was next.
Who's next?
>> Oh, that's right. The the moderator of
the comments, ladies and gentlemen, one
of the house favorites, one of the
chat's favorites. You know him, you love
him. GIVE UP MR. JIMBO SLICE. [applause]
OH, you have no idea how gnarly the chat
is. Oh my god, there's such incels. All
they want me to do, 200 people in the
chat want me to move this [ __ ] chair
into the camera. That's the level of
intellect.
It's bad. Um, I don't know. I I'm
getting old enough to where now I am
kind of considered that uncle.
Obviously, like every single person said
before me in the Steam night, but I feel
like I'm not that old. But I'm not old
enough to regularly start using the term
prostate.
>> I I know
>> you said prostate how many times in the
last 6 months?
>> Come on. You zero.
>> Let's go out back real quick.
>> No, I don't know. I just I I do think
that that term means you're getting
older when you have to say it regularly.
And I did, however, schedule a prostate
exam cuz I'm getting to that uncle age.
And I went into the doctor's office and
uh I thought it was going to be a
mundane doctor kind of like a just real
business-like in-n-out if you will.
>> But let's just say this doctor had a
little too much aloha.
I went in and he gave me a hug.
>> Didn't like that.
>> Didn't like that. And he and he said,
"Sit down." He sat me down and he gave
me two thumbs up and said, "Ready,
Freddy?"
>> REALLY DIDN'T LIKE THAT. MAN, I GOT THE
[ __ ] OUT OF THERE. I left.
>> I was not trying to find out where that
shock has been.
>> I don't know. Um, speaking of uncles, do
you guys know there's a sex offender app
now?
>> Yeah. Were you They tell you who the sex
offenders are when they live in your
area.
>> About time, right? About time. I know
mystery shaking in his boots. Calm down.
>> [laughter]
>> You know, it it's it tells you where the
sex vendors are in your area, but you
know, it's kind of [ __ ] up cuz you
have to pay 20 bucks a month or else
they blur the faces and the name.
>> Isn't that [ __ ] up? They put them
behind the wrong wall. They put them
behind a pay wall. We wanted them in
jail.
>> It's terrible. But, you know, Mystery
actually was telling me before the show
that if you pay a hundred bucks a month,
you can reblur your face in your name.
>> That's the thinker. Why do people keep
my name out?
and Mystery had something to say about
that. I know that shocks all of you.
>> I know growing up, I was born on the 4th
of July, a real firecracker.
>> I uh you know, I will tell you growing
up before July sucks. Like, spoiler
alert, Santa's not real. And I know that
hurts a lot of you or did hurt a lot of
you,
but try finding out the fireworks
weren't all for you.
>> It was very bad. Thanks, Dad.
go to school and they're like, "No, Jim,
it's not your birthday. It's this whole
place's birthday." It's all downhill
from there. That's sad. Yeah. Well, you
know what else is sad? I don't get to
watch my uncles anymore on the 4th of
July blow off firecrackers in a
telephone pole and catch it on fire and
try to pour it out with liquor.
Those were good days in the '9s.
This is so fun. Can I tell you guys what
a fever dream it is to be up here?
>> Why?
mainly because everyone stares at you
with a blank fake expecting to be very
funny and we're just up here sharing our
trauma.
It's cheaper than therapy. I drink
ginger beer. It cost me $7 to be here.
I'm poor.
>> Who else is poor?
>> Yeah, I'm sorry. That explains the bar
sales. We know. She's like, "Do you want
a menu?" I said, [laughter]
"Men?
I could barely afford Costco in bulk for
12 weeks of food. It's terrible. I'm so
poor. I did the gun trade in. You guys
see they're advertising that on the
street, which is very weird, I think.
And I'm poor, but I have a gun. Cuz
that's always the correlation, right?
Somehow I traded in my gun and the cops
gave me a $100 gift card to Foodland.
And I was walking away and I was like,
that was such a shitty deal.
>> I could have got 10 times more if I just
went into Foodland with my gun.
>> All right, everybody. My name is Jimbo
the comic. Thank you so much. Shout out
chat. Here's your [ __ ] cherry. You
weirdos.
Please pay us.
Give him Jimbo. Ladies and gentlemen,
>> I got a quick drunk one for you. I had I
have a Hawaiian uncle that's missing uh
his pinky and half of his ring finger.
Uh we called him Uncle Manu for a long
time cuz he said he got it bitten off by
a shark when he was diving. One night
we're drinking at a bar drinking next to
a a services guy and he looks at the
hand. He's like, "Hey, shark bite. Let
me see that finger." He looks at the
finger. He's like, "Bro, that's not one
shark bite. That's one turtle bite."
Goes, "Huh?" He goes, "That's not a
shark bite. Shark bites have ridges.
That's smooth. That's a turtle bite."
Why was your hand next to a turtle's
face? Were you riding turtles? My uncle
was riding turtles in the 80s before it
was fully illegal. Relax. That's all you
can you can service other people.
>> Yeah. Back in the day, people would just
ride turtles if like what you're late to
work. H you want to ride.
So then from there he was Uncle Honu and
he doesn't like that nickname. He hates
it. All right ladies and gentlemen
coming up to the stage another house
favorite. If you come here you know her.
Get up for Semile.
[applause]
>> So let's play with this chair. Huh?
not too sexy, but anyway. Um,
so I wanted to tell you a cautionary
tale today about anybody that you know
that has a little bit of high blood
pressure
or might have a heart problem. Make sure
you take your little baby aspirin
because
I'm like, [clears throat] "Ma, are you
drunk? What's going on? Did you drive
all the way home from Nepili drunk?"
So, you got to know your people and know
what's the slight difference so you can
help them out when they're having a
stroke
because [clears throat] they might look
like they're drunk, but they might be
having a stroke. So, serious folks, it's
not a joke.
So, [clears throat] me and my mom are in
recovery. We're falling in love with the
recovery. We're learning a lot through
this about our brains
and what can happen and that when that
happens. [clears throat] So, God forbid
I was the one that had a stroke because
I don't think anybody be taking care of
me, but I'm glad to be there for my mom.
So, um, yeah. And I have a dog named
Bentley. He's the best dog. He has a
bent tail and he's a he's a poodle corgi
like poodle doodle. He's an air doodle.
Air airdale doodle mix. And he's the
best dog ever. But,
and I'm on the spectrum. I have a little
thing, tiny ass burgers. So, I call
myself um I identify as having sliders.
So, sometimes I like skip the subject,
you know, all the like woo, different
subject coming up, change the subject,
try to be funny.
Um, so yeah, there's a lot of conspiracy
theories. Like back in the day, people
used to think I was weird for believing
in aliens.
I used to say, "Yeah, there's at least
four species of aliens on Earth, and
there's the originals that were the
terrarians, which are the lizards, of
course." And back in the day, they used
to tease me and think I was crazy, but
hello. Um, they're reading the AI is
reading these tablets and they're
figuring it all out. And if you get the
right the right people that they haven't
like
[ __ ] it up already. I hope we get the
honest AI, the ancient intelligence,
right? Not the artificial intelligence.
We want the agent intelligence. It's not
going to destroy it all and tell us the
truth. We need the truth. Um there's a
lot of conspiracies that's happening for
thousands and thousands of years. Um
starting with Paul from the Bible. He's
the one that [ __ ] it all up from the
beginning. Anyways,
yeah. And then um also, would you give a
15-year-old that only had a year to live
some psilocybin mushrooms? Um, [ __ ]
yeah, you would. And would you give an
82year-old lady who's had some a little
tiny bit of stroke, would you give her
some psilocybin mushrooms? [ __ ] yeah.
I'm all about that psilocybin
psychedelic therapy. So, we're waiting
patiently for mom to say okay and we'll
see we'll let you know what happens.
She's down for it. I think I told her to
to smoke a little weed because that will
help expect her the lungs with the
swallowing issue. You don't want to get
pneumonia. So, a little bit of cannabis
will help her get that out of her lungs
and she'll be healthy. So, just keep the
prayers up for mom to keep being
healthy. And my my dad's actually
starting a bank. Where was that joke?
The lady made a joke about her dad had a
bank, but last time I talked to him,
he's like, "Yeah, I'm gonna be a bank.
I'm having my own bank." I'm like, "Good
luck with that, Dad. I hope it's okay."
But yeah, that's better than dealing
cocaine like you did when I was a baby.
It was what they call the disco mafia
situation. I don't know. going up and
down the coast doing the disco with a
partner and everything and selling
cocaine
and um so yeah I'm product of that
>> and then he came to Maui
and he got saved he was now he's a born
again Christian so he taught me a lot
about Jesus my father
and if he couldn't be there at least my
heavenly father was there for me
I guess
so but the real thing is um the power is
within, right? And 9/11 was an inside
job. It's by the deep state
>> and Israel. I said it, didn't I?
>> [applause]
>> If anyone accuses this open mic as being
not open, I use that as example as
exhibit A, B, and C.
>> You can generally say whatever you want,
no matter who no matter whom agrees with
you or disagrees. Uh,
so that's it for us being monetized, but
we can try another angle in [laughter]
No, I'm not joking. They're not
monetizing us, guys. We've been trying
for months. They're not monetizing us.
So, uh, we're going to have to do this
the oldfashioned way. Uh, we'll be
filling up Molotov cocktails in the
corner. No. Um, we'll find a way to turn
this into money or not. Who gives a
[ __ ] Your, ladies and gentlemen, your
next comic uh is running a lot of AI
programs alongside of our show. I He
talks and tells me what he's doing, but
I don't understand it. And uh I tell him
to stop telling me. Maybe he'll tell
you. Ladies and gentlemen, go for Mr. E.
[laughter]
[applause and cheering]
NAH, I don't think you deserve it yet.
Couple people in the crowd. I don't
know. It ain't all you, but it's some of
you. Give it up for Chino, everyone.
Holy [ __ ] Shane Nelson can sit on stage
talking about buying hookers for kids
and want to feed him drugs and I get
called a pedophile. Can we be realistic,
Jimbo? Your girlfriend looks like a
quarter pound without cheese next to
you. You're called me a pedophile. Be
real.
[ __ ] I give I give adults sacraments to
find their healing. Come on, be
realistic. You're on the dark side. I
love my side.
Oh man.
>> Daddy. Daddy. I just hope you know
you're the one that people are praying
to stay away from the Lu Ouija board.
>> God, you're so creepy.
I don't I I I'm pretty sure it's stupid
for me to say I don't want the CIA to
get me for the Illuminati or the Masons.
Probably should change the subject. What
the hell am I talking about? I said
don't don't take my CIA. Don't ci don't
take my help. I need it.
>> God, I thought I was going to come up
and pretend to play all the drunk family
members that you could kind of learn to
laugh at. And then a couple beers in
after all my [ __ ] dickish comments, I
realized I am that drunkle.
>> So, I'm just going to be messing
[ __ ] for a minute. Man, so much
[ __ ] to roll out. Where does it stop?
Oh, man. So many things to say. Right.
It's, you know, when you have like all
the marbles trying to pour out of a
bottle at once.
>> I'm usually the opposite way with
psychedelics, but this is a nice change
of pace. I like being present.
>> Ground out with the what the earth means
for a minute, man. Normal people. Holy
cow.
>> Does anybody know what a normal person
is?
>> I found normal ones. It was that setting
on the washing machine.
Oh yeah, Danny, you know how we know
you're really not an assassin? Cuz
assassins do it from the rear.
Anyways,
man. Man, I'm coming on way too hard and
too fast. Starting to feel like
if only I was allowed to have my booze
on stage, I could just slow down, calm
down. Not allowed to bring my DMT vape
up, apparently. Where the hell are we?
When do we get to do this in Portland,
Chino?
>> I'm not trying to worry back to
Portland. That was a mean joke on you,
Chino.
>> Seriously. Seriously, I love Portland.
It doesn't know that it's not a music
festival. You can buy food cart at 4 in
the morning. There will be some
burlesque clown troop dancing somewhere.
There's definitely fire dancers. You
don't have to stop dancing for 3 days.
But the downside of anywhere, any party,
I I found out the hard way. The longer a
party goes, the larger a camp grows. If
any of you have had to make it through a
camp, get to Rainbow, you know what I'm
talking about. Oh god. It's almost as
bad as the burn. At least I know they
don't pretend to be Well, never mind. I
guess there's a lot of people trying to
pretend to be something else, but
at least Rainbow's still free. Burning
Man got so bought out, billionaires can
barely afford anymore. It's more like a
cool competition with some sexy
accessories to make it real.
How many people really believe that the
Playa still wants people to go there?
Anyone?
>> Oh, there's two of you. Wow. Out of
162,000 on Maui. Congratulations.
It's a big group.
>> I mean, don't get me wrong. I'd go to
regional burn like smaller groups of
people, less huge forest, you know.
>> Well, I mean, I like going places where
there's, you know, forest and life and
water. It's nice. Oh, man.
I didn't get enough mean jokes that I
have so many more things to say to so
many people and I don't even know where
to begin.
I guess instead of me jokes, let me
throw it out to Skyler. What a [ __ ]
G. Shroom Cat Productions. If you're on
Maui and need some real audio visual,
Shroom Cat's your cap. Real talk. He
gets the job done and then some.
>> Back on to joking.
>> No. No. One more time. Gino, where's my
highest place? I haven't been high in
three weeks. I need that Homer Simpson
chili contest buzz. Where's the Hobra?
give it to me. You know, I like it hot.
I've already crawled out of hell, so I
don't mind a little bit of peppers. But
anyways, on that note, I think I talked
too much. I got boring. So, thank you
all. Appreciate your attention. Once
again, my name's Mystery. Give it up for
Gino and everyone else. Thank you.
[applause]
>> Give it up for Cheddar Bob, ladies and
gentlemen. Mystery,
he shot his own dick. You guys don't
remember Cheddar Bob. Okay, never mind.
That just shows how old I am, I guess.
Hey, uh, somebody asked me, uh, Bashar
was asking about conspiracies earlier. I
got one for you. You guys heard of the
dead soda theory.
>> Soda used to have an expiration date of
5 to 6 years down the road. Nowadays,
it's only 2 years until your soda's
expiring. The theory, big soda hasn't
made any new new soda in the past 6
years. We're drinking six-year-old soda.
Thank you. Someone who knows that the
soda's been flatter and flatter year by
year. You don't notice it when it's
incremental, but when you notice it, you
notice it. Ladies and gentlemen, someone
who notices it. Coming to stage, MR.
CHUCK SAUCE. CHUCK THOMPSON. [applause]
[applause]
Sweet soda joke, bro.
That's good. I like sodas. I'm actually
from Minnesota, so we got that going for
us.
Wow. Aloha everybody. The few, the
proud, the people that were here after
Mr. Eve set. Give yourself a round of
applause everybody. [applause]
I was like, why the [ __ ] are is everyone
still here? And then I realized it was
dumping outside and I'm like, all right,
nice. Also, for hippies, not enough of
your white stuff. What's going on with
that? Okay.
Um, I don't want to do a whole lot of
political jokes, but I do think it's
funny that the Straight of Hormuz was
closed by the gayest people ever.
>> All right, [laughter]
that's good. This guy's just arguing
over his bar tab. That's nice. That's
I'm glad you could hear that more than
anyone else. He's literally never
getting laid, but let's talk about
geopolitical politics and stuff.
[laughter]
It's fantastic. It's good. Also, [ __ ]
muse.
That sounds like 500 bucks an hour. Am I
right? Okay. All right. We're getting
there. We're doing it.
Guys, I've been wounded. I'm a wounded
warrior.
Look. Look at me. I'm wounded. Look at
this. Look at that. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Get it.
I cut my finger off two and a half weeks
ago, guys. You guys ever cut a finger
off?
I cut it off
and I went into uh the urgent care,
which spoiler alert, urgent care is
neither of those things.
I went to the minute medical. I don't
like doctors that misspell the word
minute.
You're like, YOU GOT MEDICAL? COOL.
We're minute.
[laughter]
I should have just gone to the church
across the street.
But uh yeah, I cut my finger on a
mandolin. I was watching Captain
Carelli's mandolin and I just was like
going to kill myself. Okay, just
kidding. THAT SHE YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
THAT YO, IT'S NOT FOR NOTHING. GET OUT
OF THE WAY.
YOU'RE ALWAYS IN THE WAY. YOU'RE WEARING
A SWEATER. IT'S 79°.
It's zipped up all the way. What's going
on there?
>> So, Captain Carelli's Mandolin stars
Nicholas Cage,
and he clearly did that movie to buy a
castle.
That's good. I like that you're wearing
a police uniform. I really appreciate
that. You you you're wearing a police
uniform. Some people call it a wife
beater, but um you know, to each their
own.
It's good. I cut my finger off every I
wasn't supposed to yell, but I'm just
I'm I'm toning it down. Also, there was
a girl WEARING A BUTTERFLY OUTFIT FOR 18
MINUTES. What was going on there?
Butterflies in the sky. I could fly
twice as high. We're clearly smoking the
same math. Okay.
I cut my finger off on a mandolin, which
is like uh it's not a musical
instrument. Or is the people in the
urgent Medicare thought it was like a
fish,
>> which doesn't make me feel good about
science or technology. Are you guys
familiar what a mandolin is?
>> It's like a horizontal
uh Hold on. Let me check my notes. Hold
on a second. Hold on. HOLD ON. HOLD ON.
WAIT, WAIT.
>> Let's go. It's This paper is unlike my
wife. It's very wet. Hold on.
>> I can't read this. Can you read this?
What does that say?
>> Horizontal guillotine for vesicles.
>> Vegetables. What are you [ __ ] stupid?
I'M JUST KIDDING. I DON'T KNOW HOW TO
SPELL VEGETABLES.
SO, UH, G, UH, mandolin is a horizontal
what?
>> Vegetable slicer.
>> It's a horizontal guillotine for
vegetables.
So, I was meal prepping, right? I got my
cucumbers.
I got my summer squash.
I got my Mitch McConnell's.
And I cut off my [ __ ] finger. And uh
I had to go to the urgent care and they
put my hand in a big shoe box full of
like iodine or whatever and I was like
rostafare and then uh they're like do
you see how much you're bleeding and I'm
like yes I see how much I'M BLEEDING.
ALSO SIDE NOTE I I FEEL LIKE AN OLD MAN.
I WENT INTO THE [ __ ] CLINIC and I had
like a basketball size amount OF PAPER
TOWELS COVERED IN BLOOD.
And then I open the door and I go in and
they ask me for my phone number and
they're like, "Cool. We're going to text
you a link. YOU GOT TO DOWNLOAD THE APP,
FILL OUT your information, and then
we'll see you."
I HAVE LOST A FINGER.
MY WIFE IS PISSED,
>> RIGHT?
>> She's still trying to park. That's not
good. They put my hand in the big thing
on iodine and they're like, "Do you see
how much you're bleeding?" And I'm like,
"Yes, I see how much I'm bleeding." And
I don't know a lot about medical
technical terms, so I'm going to
reiterate in the terms that I hear in my
brain. They see they say like, "Hey, do
you notice that your hoopa boop is
slightly detached from your boopa boop?"
And I'm like, "Yes, I do see that my
hoopa boop is completely detached from
my boopa boop." And they're like,
"That's not good."
And then they're like, "You're bleeding
a lot. Do you know that you're bleeding
a lot?" And I'm like, "Yes, I know that
I'm bleeding a lot." And they're like,
"You should go to a hospital.
Bro.
>> So, I got like four stitches in here.
ALSO, HOW does Maui have 15 golf courses
but a quarter of a hospital?
I'm a stoner. So, that's 7 g of
hospital.
It's not enough. All right, that's my
time. It's your Rosemary. Have a lovely
night everybody. And from me to you.
Hello. [screaming]
I need a finger.
>> Chuck sauce. Chuck saus. Ladies and
gentlemen. [cheering]
See, Chuck, I could tell you lost weight
and it was a finger. All right.
Mandolin his finger.
>> You didn't cut it. You julianed it.
That's what happens. You [ __ ] coined
your pinky. [laughter]
>> Oh my god. Yeah, imagine that falling in
the pack of carrots. It's like, "Oh,
which one's the thing?" All right, never
mind. Ladies and gentlemen, uh this is
the last comedian on the list. So, if
you want to go up, tonight's the night.
We got a little extra time on here. Put
your name on the list. If not, you're
ending up with this as your last man,
the man of many voices, uh including a
lot of them that sound like Chewbacca.
Get ready.
>> [applause]
>> I actually saw Chuck at the hospital
>> and he told me what happened and I
totally [ __ ] cracked up at the
thought of Chuck
>> ripping so hard on the mandolin.
>> A small guy playing mandolin like he's
rocking out guitar stylist. Okay, for
the cesspool chat, I'm going to give you
some some fodder for the cannon.
Talk about
having do you chewing double mint gum,
having fun on the run. That's a double
man bun. I I bet you guys didn't think
you would hear I don't think I didn't
think you No one in here thought that
you'd be hearing jokes from the Witcher
tonight. And I know one thing for sure.
The chat's going to be like maybe he can
use his magic to get laughter.
[laughter]
Uh so so Trump's got this this thing,
Midnight Hammer. Did you hear about
that? [laughter]
That sounds like Honey Girl's uh married
local brother side piece. Oh, why even?
It's like code, you know, between the
girlfriends. Oh, are you going to see
Midnight Hammer tonight?
Oh, brother. Um, this is just th this
has been just an amazing ride. I love,
you know, you never know what's going to
happen, you know, over here. I I want to
throw out a couple acronyms for PA.
Polynesians aggressively intimidate
Anglo-Saxons.
Pathfinders and Isuzu's abandoned.
Uh,
well, let me see what else was I going
to talk. Let me just glance at my
scenario here. What? I I don't want to
miss any bullet points. Oh, uncle. Duh.
Uh, yeah. So, my uncle Earl, he's really
a funny guy. He uh this is no joke. He
would actually do this. He worked at at
Chets's Hardware. And this girl, this
lady came in, don't laugh, but but do
you have any any mothballs? And he goes,
"No, but we have a large assortment of
butterfly nuts."
Uh, why is it that Oh, do you think
Ariana Grande will graduate
to Ariana Vente?
>> Stupid. Stupid. Um,
uh, why is it that all the drug
companies sound like rappers now? It's
like, yo, Wii, head over to Sky Rizzy's,
grab the Escalade so we can go to
Madna's afterparty,
right? It's just, it sounds funny that
like the rappers are naming naming
medicines now. Um, I I heard they did a
new a new uh Pelaton.
>> Anybody hear about that? Pelaton murder
one. That's all. Pick up the gun.
Change trigger figures. Pick up the gun.
Pelaton Murder One. Best way to break a
sweat. Okay. Uh, we got [laughter]
I I had this crazy amazing dream. You
guys know about Tibetan throat singing?
I had this incredible dream. I'm in I
I'm I'm hiking through the Himalayas.
I'm just like, "Oh my god, I'm find I'm
I'm I'm following this sound. It's like
resonating in my head. It's so
beautiful. It's just amazing." And and
I'm just like [clears throat]
I woke up. It turned out to be my my
girl's vibrator against my head.
Disappointing in so many ways, but it it
made me want to go to Tibet now, right?
But you know, I hear they make a good
mudslide.
Oh [ __ ]
>> Oh,
okay. Uh, I got Hilo airport. Okay. Hilo
airport is so moldy.
>> How moldy is it?
>> It's so moldy that if you are allergic
to
what the hell is that medication mold
made out of freaking
>> penicellin?
>> Penicellin. If you're allergic to
penicellin, you're going to need EpiPen
and a ride to the hospital. That's how
moldy it is. But I will say something
about
it's it's amazing over there. They have
the most beautiful the only airport in
the world you're going to see live
hoola. Two uncles playing
bring aloha
aloha.
Boy,
flight 297 to Honolulu now boarding the
premier club members and all wheelchair
bound passengers.
[singing]
Uh all other passengers needing
pre-boarding registration for flight to
Mokai, please line up along concourse B,
left side, gate 5. Anyway, it they
didn't miss a beat and you guys don't
either. We're out on a Monday night.
Why? Because we somehow didn't spend our
entire paycheck like we used to. Aloha
everybody. Love you. [applause]
>> Yeah, absolutely.
Double man bun himself, Eddie V. Ladies
and gentlemen,
[applause]
what did you accomplish with the second
man bun that you couldn't have done with
a bigger first man bun? I want to know
WHAT NECESSITATES A SECOND MAN BUN. I
MUST KNOW.
SORRY, I I'm under a little stress. I
have a friend that's building a pool in
their backyard and uh the the county
zoned their pool so much smaller than
they wanted it. It's like a little
Musabe pool. It's literally as big as
these three tables and the triangle
across. That's the Musubi pool. They
have a whole backyard and all they can
get is a little Mushab pool. It's a
triangle they can swim from corner to
corner to corner. They don't EVEN HAVE A
FOURTH CORNER, JUST three corners of a
pool.
And I was like, "That's terrible. How
that's that's tiny. How deep is it
allowed to be?" They're like, "Oh, they
didn't specify." And I'm like, "There's
where you get your real estate.
>> You drill that pole deep.
>> You drill that pool so deep that they
don't see a bottom.
And you don't light the bottom either.
You just strike fear into their heart
when they go and check out the pool for
for regulations.
Like, hey, uh, all right. This pool's
the property. How deep is this pool?"
Like, rumor has it. Nobody knows.
>> Some say it doesn't have a bottom. Can
you drop a glow stick and just watch it
disappear? Like, how deep is this pool?
>> As deep as your fear. That's how deep it
is. Fear pool. That's what I call that
joke. All right,
>> we got one more person doing a quick
two-minute set. You guys ready for one
more comment closing out the night?
[applause]
>> Ah, yes. I love the reluctance. It's
happening anyways. Get used to it.
Coming to the stage, Jimbo's roommate.
He shares his space with an earlier
comic. Give it up for Mr. Jamie.
[applause]
>> My landlord.
>> Um, I am Jimbo's landlord,
but I can't afford to not live at the
house, so we also live together.
[laughter]
That's that's just the life, you know.
Um, I just want to start by saying I'm
not a comic, so don't laugh, please. Uh,
and if you can keep the camera like like
waist high, like like higher than my
legs, please. I don't I don't I skipped
leg day. Um, what was I going to say?
Oh, yeah. So, if anyone saw me like
across the the room and was like, "He's
mildly attractive." Uh, it's all about
the change, okay? Just let me talk a
little bit. Um, oh, also, Franny, it's
nice to see you again.
>> Hi. Isn't that Franny?
>> Hi, Franny. I took your marine biology
class in college. It was one of my
favorite classes ever.
I I just can't remember to say that.
>> Are you kidding her?
>> Yeah, I I was too scared to come up to
you. I just wanted to be here.
Um
>> kiss.
>> Yeah. So, drunk drunkles. Drunk uncles.
We had a drugged uncle. He does a lot of
drugs and he sits right there a lot. Um
yeah, he's cool. Me and Mr. are really
good friends. We've been friends for a
long time. I don't know. Oh, there he
is. Hey, buddy. Yeah. Oh, he flipped me
off. Oh,
>> what was my last name?
>> Um, E. [laughter]
Mr. Space E. Um, where'd you get that
outfit? Mystery Goodwill.
>> Your mom gave it to me.
>> Out of my I haven't talked to my mom in
10 years, but I try. I do have mommy
issues. Let's get that out of the books.
You know what I'm saying? If you didn't
think that, now you know it. Um, oh
yeah, drunk uncles. So, u my uncles are
like 90 years old. So, if they drank,
they would probably die.
But that's besides the point. We're
talking about drunk uncles here. Um, it
hasn't been 2 minutes yet. I only get 2
minutes on stage, as you can see why.
So, for the next 13 seconds, I'm going
to say this. Um, thank you all for
enjoying this baby and sitting through
it definitely. That was that was fun.
Um, and have a great night. Thanks. Bye.
[applause]
Get up for Jamie. Ladies and gentlemen,
>> you don't you don't talk to your mommy.
>> Me neither.
>> Yeah. Hell yeah. Hell yeah.
>> Weird pitch. We should [ __ ] each other's
moms. Just [laughter]
>> blind.
>> That Why would that matter?
>> Why would that matter?
>> Hell yeah,
>> dude. What a weird way to start that
conversation. All right. Well, I mean,
what's your favorite color? That's
certainly no joke. All right, guys. Uh,
anybody else want to go up and do some
comedy tonight? [laughter]
>> We're calling it as a good night. Hey,
ladies and gentlemen, give it up for
yourselves.
[applause]
>> Okay, cool. I just wanted to see if your
low reaction energy was for you as well
as it is for us. It's okay. No, you guys
did great. It's been a Monday night. You
guys are fantastic. We had 25,000 people
watch this show online.
Why? Right. Why? You got a question?
>> Who wins the hot sauce?
>> Oh, you're you're absolutely right. It
is the time. It is the time. I mean, you
guys you guys you guys are all in the
runningings. Uh have you won hot sauce
before you two over there?
>> Cuz you've been to several shows. So,
that that's one. I got one more bottle.
Let's see. You guys both went to the
show last night, too, right? Man, this
is going to be a tough one. I'm going to
find out how to divvy this up. these
three, you guys in this triangle. We're
all going to give you prizes.
Congratulations to this triangle of
people, the Bermuda Triangle of Human
Beings. Uh, thank you so much for
joining us tonight. Um, I hope you had a
good time. If you did, please tell your
friends. And if you didn't, shut your
[ __ ] mouth. We don't need rumors. It
is a small island. It gets around fast.
Uh, this happens every Monday night.
What should we do for next week's theme?
Any suggestions?
>> Anybody want a theme? Should we just uh
>> [ __ ] neighbor? Should we just try
hard next week? Is next week theme? Try
really hard.
>> All right, we're going to do best
material next week. So, everybody type
five is your best material. What was
that?
>> Funny.
>> Funny. [laughter] Funny. Yeah. If only
it were that easy, you know.
>> US citizens traveling.
>> US citizens traveling. Oh, no. That that
used to be funnier. Now it is uh it is
visible. Now, we'll do we'll do a tight
material. So, everybody bring your tight
material. Um, I'm going to talk to the
chat room in a second. Oh, Jimbo is
about to tell me who won the hot sauce
online. So, stick around online. We'll
tell you who won hot sauce and we'll
figure out how to get that to you. Once
again, if you want to buy some hot sauce
online, check out the website
highspice.com.
Use the coms sim 10 promo code to get
10% off your order. Um, just like our
first order that came in a couple weeks
ago. God, I was trying to remember her
name. It was such a weird one. It was
cool. She's from New Mexico. I don't
remember. Starts with a gal. Dude,
appreciate you. Thank you so much. Um,
I'll remember your name next week and
then I'll tell everybody your name and
people are going to bother you. No. Uh,
thank you so much for joining us. We'll
see you next week. Love you. Bye. See
you. [cheering]
[applause]
>> End simulation.
>> No, I'm laugh.
It wasn't funny. It was too personal.
>> That's a joke. And I switched the person
every
>> Well, I'm just telling you how I take it
or
what you're going to say.
I know.
Good. Good.
>> Way to ruin the vibe all
>> vibe killer.
>> I just can recognize it.
>> Yeah, the vibe
of you always ruining it. Yeah, I
recognize it.
>> Me the only nice one to you. You bite
the hand. That's nice. just nice to me
and you're the only person that pays
attention to me. Dude, are you that
[ __ ] ego?
>> Dude, don't [ __ ] talk to me. Keep my
name out your [ __ ] mouth.
>> I will ask you for advice in Instagram
again. Why don't you have the chat? Let
me show the Instagram DM.
>> Here, let's go. Let's watch the
Instagram.
>> I'll pull it up for the chat.
>> Uh, Jimbo, can you give me advice?
>> I asked if he had advice for myself.
>> Yeah.
>> Dad, that was a compliment. I'm trying
to be nice.
>> Yeah. Okay.
>> Don't worry. You don't have to see that
again. You get the real me now.
>> Thank God, bro.
>> The real you.
>> You'll see the real me. Look at this
guy. Can't take a joke. It's unreal.
>> Neither can you,
>> bro. Not at all.
>> I just gave one drag. You want to come
at me harder?
>> I'm sure you will, Don. The chat. Look.
Go get your AI on the chat.
Sorry you had to hear that, chat.
[laughter]
They like the They like the drama.
>> Chat, I'm so sorry. Okay, who won the
comment of night? Would it be wrong if I
gave the person who dog mystery the
hardest the chat member of the night?
Focus on it.
This is me being nice.
>> I'm a real one, Skylar.
>> Oh, the chat's going nuts.
That's I'm about to get the chair. I'm
about to break the chair over his dome.
All right, we got to announce the
comment at night and I get out of here
and go cry.
>> Oh, sorry. Sorry.
>> I'm letting Chino pick. I got the
finalist. I'm letting Chino pick.
>> I love you guys. I can't even keep up. I
got yelled at by a crackhead.
down.
>> All right, Chino, we got some finalist
for you, dog.
>> Yeah. Who we got for finalist? What's
up, everybody?
>> Yeah. All right. What's up, chat? Thanks
for joining us tonight. Uh, hope you
like the show. Or if you didn't, I hope
you didn't like it. Um, that's all part
of it, too. It's important to understand
how to manage your disappointment. It's
a big part of life. I don't know if you
noticed, but disappointment is a
prevalent thing right now. All the
things we like are turning to [ __ ]
>> Everything from sports gambling to
Pokemon.
>> That is a intro of all intros.
>> Yeah, sorry. We want Chino. Well, you
get Chino Allstar. Hey, now
>> they're all freaking out cuz me and
Mystery got into a fight on camera.
>> Oh, I heard it. I heard it from over
there. I was going to tell, hey, take
that outside, but then I realized
they're doing in front of the camera
like
actually.
>> We got finalists.
>> Yeah. Who are the finalists? I know
Donnie Boy was one of them, right?
Donnie boy. So, I'm going to give him
I'm going to give them all some shine.
>> All right,
>> we got Sun-Kissed 335. And I cannot
confirm if this is a fully original
comment. I did get a little feedback in
the chat, but Sun-Kissed comment was
about this comic and they said her hair
looks like Darth Vader's helmet.
>> Oh, for Sasha. Yeah, they said,
[laughter]
>> "Who was that?"
>> Uh, that was Suniss 335.
>> Yo, I saw Suniss actually lighting up
the boards. Good stuff, Suniss.
I appreciate you guys. Thank you. Sorry,
I'm just reading comments.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Which is what I'm told as a
comedian we should never do, but here we
are.
>> We had a lot of people make fun of Danny
for saying suffocate, which
>> suffocate
>> just deserves a shout out.
>> Yo. Okay. I can fully understand that
because I used to work at Chili's for a
little while when I was living in LA and
someone said uh smashed potatoes. And I
was like, "Oh, you want mashed
potatoes?" They're like, "Yes, smashed
potatoes." And they said it like four
times like corrected me. And then they
ate them like smashed potatoes and it it
stuck with me. It still sticks with me.
>> It's
they would stick to you. Um Rock James
had a good comment about you. Rock James
1 said Chino resembles one of the
missing links in the human Neanderthal.
>> It's true. [laughter] It's true. Sandy.
No. Hold on. Apparently I've been What
does it say here?
>> Acknowledge Allison's email. What did
Did I miss an email from you? Allison,
I'm so sorry. If I did, I will email you
back from the comedy simulator page. I
never check the emails for that, so I
apologize. Um, but I will check it out
now. And Alzen, you're one of our
>> also who emailed frequent viewers.
>> Roll up. DM us.
>> Yeah, slide. [laughter]
Slide homie. No. No. I I'll check the
email. Sorry about that.
>> It's ridiculous.
>> Do you think the comedians could survive
their set time in the chat afterwards?
No. No. Dude, it takes years to build up
defenses like these. Are you kidding me?
>> I have tough skin. I hate myself worse
than you will. I have I have a white tea
cell count as somebody on prep. You're
not [ __ ] with me. You can't even try.
Can't even try. And if you even
understand that joke, you're probably on
Grinder, just so you know. Um
>> my girlfriend's going to leave me.
>> Do you know? [laughter] No. No. She just
left. You're too late.
>> She just left for the evening. Uh who
who else we got on the board?
>> Hey, this is biased because it's about
mystery, but I Sorry, guys. I picked
this before he yelled at me. Okay,
trust. Uh Donny Boy 24 said that if he
was the human centipede, he'd volunteer
for the middle. H the center spot. Oh
yeah, we call that a fullback in our in
our neighborhood.
[laughter]
>> We call that a bossy bottom.
>> Henry OP. Henry OP, a legend. OG in the
chat.
>> Yeah, Henry's been killing it, too. I
saw his name pop up a bunch.
>> Henry called Chuck a GameStop manager.
[laughter]
>> Ooh. You know what's funny? Like even
though that's like his assumed job, you
know what his real job is? He sells
mattresses.
>> Close. the He looks like a mattress
seller for sure. Uh, by the way, these
are gifts from Semile.
>> She gave me a couple of uh
>> There's a meaning in there.
>> Twootie Pops. [laughter] Uh, well,
they're for me to suck.
>> That's a deeper meaning.
>> We'll find out. I guess I'm the sucker
here.
>> Somehow that's racist. I don't know.
[laughter]
>> Circle of life. Uh, I almost smuffed
that. [laughter]
>> They're evolving the word. I love it.
>> Now it's the word smuffer. [laughter] Uh
uh so I think Donniey's going to win
because Donnie had two in the finals.
Donnie had uh with Chuck uh he looks
like he should have Patrick Star's
voice.
[laughter]
>> So I think Donnie I think Donnie
>> So Donnie Donnie you are a winner
tonight. Check us out on uh since I'm
already checking the email comedy
simulator@gmail.com
or check out our Instagram comedy
simulator. Drop us a line. Uh I'll get
you some hot sauce if you live in
America. If you don't, I'm sorry. We
live in a dictatorship. There's nothing
I can do for you. Uh if you have an
American fence that can cross the border
for you wherever you may be, then yeah,
like definitely hook them up. Make it
happen. Uh leave the last S for so
unfunny. Right on, Diablo. Appreciate
you. You got your sauce last week. Hope
you loved it. Um somebody said they were
waiting on a sauce. I uh
>> Is that Allison who said that?
>> No, no, no. It was uh I forget.
>> Oh, Allison did some art for us.
>> OH, I CAN'T WAIT TO CHECK THAT OUT.
DUDE, I am so stoked. Allison
toilet. It's just like a really
>> I don't care. It could be me eating
turds out of the bowl. I don't care. I'm
just so flattered.
>> And a bunch of [ __ ] coming down.
>> You have no idea. I love myself so much
that watching cartoons of me doing
horrible things is just as good. Like
I'm cool with it.
>> You heard it. This is an open invitation
chat.
Caricature contest for Chino. Okay.
>> Hey, you know what?
>> Take a good look at this.
>> Hey, take a photo. Make AI porn.
[laughter]
>> I You're not getting
>> I want I want you to make AI porn.
>> Hey, give him a yam. Okay, I got to go.
I Tino will close you out. I love you,
Chad. Thank you, bro.
>> This guy doesn't get enough credit. He's
a legend.
>> Oh, I get plenty of credit. I get too
much credit. Um, appreciate it, guys.
All right, we're going to close out. If
you guys go ahead and uh give your
closing statements in the chat, we'll
bring them up. What we got here? Uh, so
I promised Allison I will check out that
art and I'll give a shout out next week.
Who knows? It might become a graphic if
if if it's what we've been talking about
on here. Um, we're going to make the
chair the uh new logo pretty soon. So,
you guys want it? You got it. The chair
is going to be front and center at all
times. Right where it says comedy
simulator at the bottom of the screen
like right down there where it says
comedy simulator. We'll probably have
like a little little chair like right
like right there cuz the clock goes
here. We're in a little Comedy Simulator
chair right here. Little blah something
like that. Um, should be fun. Yeah. Hey,
thanks SCL. appreciate you. Yes, it
involves the chair. Allison, you're
saying good words to me. Appreciate it.
Me, Henry. OP. Henry, didn't did we give
you sauce before or didn't we like try
to give you sauce? Uh, if we tried
before, let's try again. Um, yeah, great
work. Love hate from Canada. Hey, thank
you, Slice. Uh, it's a lovehate for us,
too, because we love Canadians, but uh,
man, when you guys come vacation here,
you're kind of annoying, but we need
your money. So, like, please don't don't
forget us. Uh mystery is going to watch
Ninja Turtles and come back and watch
Yeah. Watch your back, Jimbo. Uh yeah,
he's going to go full Casey on him. Uh
Casey Anthony, not Casey from um You
mean he's going to ch kill children?
[laughter]
[clears throat] Uh I'm having a bad
week. My dad just passed away. Can you
get a ghost? Oh, I'm so sorry, Johnny.
There's your
ghost fart for your missing person. Sick
chair, bro. Dude, the chair is [snorts]
sick. Um, chair is sick as always. Uh,
chairastic. I agree, Henry. Chairastic,
dude. We love you. Um, just emailed each
other. All right. Awesome. Yeah. Oh,
that's right. We had to set up the
correspondence. Never got the sauce out.
Let's fix that. I got you. Uh, I'll send
you a bunch of stickers and [ __ ] too.
Uh, watch out for Mr. E in the parking
lot. Uh, you know. Yeah, you should be
careful. That's where he dwells. No, I'm
just joking. Uh, we all talk after the
show. Um, we'll see. I'm sure
everybody's fine. Um, see Johnny, sorry
bro. We love you. All good. Yeah. Hey
Johnny. Whether I I mean I'm sure you're
telling the truth. He didn't say it, but
even if you weren't. Um, good troll. But
here's that ghost fart one more time.
That was a little low one. Um,
yeah. All right. We did do kind of smoke
with me.
Where you at, Orbius? I'll smoke with
you, bro. I'm I'm about to go smoke
right now and then go to the gym cuz I'm
a psychopath. I want to see an old lady
up there doing some old lady jokes and I
think the older people will get the more
material they have from their lives. I
agree that older people are naturally
funnier just because they have more to
draw from. Um but you know like it's
like uh there's not as many older people
these days willing to get in front of
the camera anymore because some of you
guys have been so mean to them. Um you
know I won last week but I didn't want
the the hot sauce but you want the
stickers. Oh, okay. I never loot. So,
you're not not a hot sauce person. We
want stickers. Cool. Uh, send me a
message. Uh, we'll send you a little
envelope with all of our hot highspice
stickers. And, uh, I think also you're
going to start some comedy simulator
stickers. One of the ideas that Skyler
and I had brought up once, I think, is
that we're talking about doing like
trading cards. Um, like comedy simulator
cards and any comedian that comes on the
show can be carded. Uh, I think that'd
be pretty cool. Little collector set,
make a couple holographics. Um, I mean,
like I said earlier, everything is being
ruined. Like people who collect cards,
like Pokemon is being ruined by the
collectors and the children aren't
getting it. You know, maybe we can have
something collectible so we can ruin
that. Uh, the gym. Yep, that's right.
Radio, the Radio Star. I go to the gym
after this every week because uh I can't
sleep. I just think of all the horrible
things that somebody said about me. No.
Uh, I have I have adrenaline and uh I'm
caffeine sensitive. So, if I had
caffeine today, I need to grind on it
out. Right on, everybody. Thank you so
much for joining us. I love that you
guys still watch the show some nights. I
don't know why, but I'm so happy to have
you here. You guys have been dope. Um,
I'm setting up the Aahu show very soon.
We are working that. I am in the talks.
We are going to get a date soon. So,
soon we will give you guys some
comedians from another range so you can
see new comedy. Uh, and then eventually
once we get those kinks worked out,
we'll be coming to your neighborhood.
So, don't forget to chat in the chat and
tell us where you want us to be. Maybe
we'll come see you soon. Uh, we'll do a
comedy simulator comedy simulator out
there and then while I'm out there, I'll
probably do like a headlining show or
something so you guys can come check it
out. All you people complaining that you
don't see me do enough comedy, you'll
actually get to see a full set. It's way
better than what I do here. Right on,
guys. Have a great night. Thank you so
much for tuning in. Uh, we'll see you
next week, every Monday. Subscribe so
that you get the notification every
Monday this happens. 7:15 our time,
wherever you may be in the world. 7:15
Hawaii time. Shoots. Good seeing you.
Have a good night.
>> I read the chat for a minute.
>> Yeah. Wild, right?
>> Some guy called you Cheeto and I just
lost it.
>> Oh, I [laughter]
>> I don't know.
>> That's like not even Some people have
said some horrible things.
>> Oh, yeah. But it's always with like
>> I'm glad today was mostly about the
chair